威尔 · 森坦斯: 让我们进入结对编程的人们,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's go
into Pair Programming folks,
我们会先遇到这些东西
we're gonna start encountering
these things first, and
然后，事后，实际解决它们，看看它们是如何工作的。
then, afterwards, actually resolving
them and seeing how they work.
所以你会首先看到高阶函数
So you're gonna start seeing
high order functions first, and
然后我们自己解决。
then we're gonna start actually
resolving them ourselves.
所以，我们要使用结对编程来做到这一点，这是迄今为止和
So, we're gonna use Pair Programming
to do so, this is by far and
作为一个工程师，最有效的成长方式。
away the most effective way
to grow as an engineer.
如果你以前做过，你可能已经知道这一点，但是
If you've done it before,
you probably already know this, but
我们要用一种非常有效的方法。
we're going to do it in
a really effective way here.
看看这个，如果你想把自己打造成一个工程师,
Take a look at this, if you
are building yourself as an engineer,
你经常会陷入两个非常危险的陷阱。
you fall into often two very risky traps.
一个是研究者，一个是堆叠叠花，两者都是
One is the researcher and
one is the Stack Overflower, both
正在逃避成为一名工程师的真正意义，我马上就会告诉你们。
are avoiding what it really is to be an
engineer, which I'll tell you in a second.
研究人员避免成为一名工程师,
The researcher avoids what
it is to be an engineer,
就是能够击中整个街区并以某种方式解决它,
which is to be able to hit a whole
block and somehow resolve through it,
这就是作为一个工程师的全部，我们到底要怎么做呢？
that is all it is to be an engineer,
how do we actually do that?
我早该想到的我们应该这么做,
I should have figured out,
here's how we do it,
这是我们如何实际解决打击整个街区，我们通过代码。
here's how we actually resolve hitting
a whole block we go through the code.
当我们在那个一行一行地阻塞我们并且理解数据的位上时，他们
When we on that bit that's blocking us
line by line and understand the data, they
我们称之为状态，当你一行一行地查看活动数据时，这就是调试。
call it the state, the live data as you go
through line by line, that is debugging.
它会命中一个块并假设代码，然后进行控制台日志记录
It's hitting a block and assuming
the code, and then console logging
使用其他调试工具，一行一行地查看数据。
essential using some other debugging tool,
the data as you go through, line by line.
虽然我们喜欢避免这样做,
We love to avoid doing that though,
我们会不惜一切代价避免这个过程，我们会养成这样的习惯
we will do anything to avoid doing that
process, we gonna get in that habit of
我们会尽一切努力，包括这里的一两件事。
doing so we'll do anything we can,
including one or two these things here.
我们成为了研究者，那个障碍，我们看到了神秘的一面,
We become the researcher, that block,
we look at the mystery bit,
也许是个新的关键词。
maybe it's a new key word.
在接下来的三天里，我们阅读了所有关于
And we spend the following three
days reading every last thing about
新的关键词，以及原型链的所有方面，非常棒。
the new keyword, and about all aspects
of the prototype chain, and wonderful.
然而，我们不写一行代码，我们避免了块,
And yet we don't write a single
line of code, we avoid the block,
另一种方法是从 Stack Overflow 获取代码片段来修复 bug。
the other approach is to grab snippets of
code to fix a bug from Stack Overflow.
当我们插上电源不能工作时,
And when that one when we plug it in,
doesn't work,
把这段加上我们加进去的部分。
take that snippet plus the bit we added.
把它放到 Stack Overflow 中，然后说，这些位是如何粘在一起的？
Put it in the Stack Overflow, and say,
how do these bits, stick together?
两者都不是有效的，都是作为一个工程师所必需的,
Neither is effective in its own isolation,
both are necessary to being an engineer,
你们在职业生涯的第一年就这么做了，这两个都是。
you've done this in the first year
of your careers, both of these.
可能是这样的，是的，就是这样的，但是你必须要做得更好
That's probably, yeah, that's how it is,
but you've gotta get better at
平衡这两者，以及最重要的部分。
balancing those two and the really
important bit which is just going through.
并在控制台日志的帮助下逐行分析代码
And analyzing the code yourself line by
line by line with the help of console logs
或者调试工具的帮助。
or the help of some
sort of debugging tool.
然后，是的，去理解和
And then yes, going to understand and
建立你的基本原则，理解这就是研究者。
building your underlying principles
understanding that's the researcher.
但是有时候你会说，我不知道它是怎么工作的,
And yet taking snippets that sometimes
you just go, I don't know how it works,
是魔法，但它的工作，这是一个工程师的一部分，但
is magic but it works,
that’s part of being an engineer but
你得保持平衡。
you gotta get that balance right.
这样做的途径是结对编程,
And the route to do so
is Pair Programming,
你可以解决困难的问题，还有个同伙和你一起犯罪。
you get to tackle tough blocks and
you got a partner in crime alongside you.
你必须专注于手头的问题，因为你不能逃避。
You get to stay focused on the problem
at hand because you can’t run away.
去泡一杯茶因为他们就坐在你旁边,
To make a cup of tea, because they're
literally sitting there right beside you,
你也不能花太多时间做这些事。
and you also can't spend too
much time doing these things.
所以研究人员,
So the researcher,
我仍然记得我第一次和一个叫约翰的人进行结对编程。
I still remember my first time pair
programming with a guy called John.
他坐在我旁边
And he sits next to me, and
他说，你不介意我们先研究一下这个吧。
he's like, do you mind if we do some
sort of reading up on this first.
我说当然然然后大概8分钟他说,
And I said of course, and
then like eight minutes he then says,
你介意我开始吗
do you mind if I get started, and
我想要读完每一本书，我想先全部理解，对吗？
I was like I wanted to read up on every,
I wanna understand it all first, right?
我做不到，我的搭档在等我
I couldn't, my partner was waiting for
我他们准备运行，我也不能只是给他们一个代码片段。
me they were ready to run, I also
couldn't just give them a code snippet.
我记得有一次我在处理纸张，有一个叫爱丽丝的人
I remember a time I was working with
paper and someone called Alice and
我不能只给他们一个代码片段。
I couldn't just give them a code snippet.
因为他们不告诉我为什么要用这个,
Because they were like, won't talk
me through why we're using this,
它是如何解决问题的。
how it's solving the problem.
当我们结对编程来表达和解释我们的代码时，我们就是傻瓜
We are fools when we pair programming
to verbalize and explain our code and
因此，不仅使它单独工作的一些元素，但
therefore not just make it work
alone some element of that but
理解我们所做的。
understanding as we go.
这是另一个重要的部分，它将改进我们的技术沟通,
And that's the other big piece here, it's
gonna refine our technical communication,
我们的配对程序是这样的。
the way we pair program is this.
如果我是导航员，我会看提示符，然后
If I'm navigator,
I'm looking at the prompt and
我看到它说，我让 twitteapi 变得很酷。
I'm seeing it says,
I make it cool to Twitte API.
我现在要带领我的伴侣，他们的手放在键盘上打字
I'm now going to lead my partner their
hands are on the keyboard typing and
实际上执行代码本身
actually executing the code itself and
然后口头解释一个策略，他们必须变成实际的代码。
then verbally explain a strategy that
they must turn into actual code.
他们不能下车，他们不能做到他们的方式，他们必须采取我的解释和
They can't get off, they can't do it their
way they have to take my explanation and
如果他们不理解我的解释,
implement it and if they're not
understanding my explanation,
这都是我的功劳。
that's all in me.
我不能说，嘿，实际上，让我告诉你怎么做,
I can't say, hey, actually,
let me just show you how to do it,
我必须能够如此清晰地表达出来
I've got to be able to
verbalize with such clarity and
精确的直观风格，我的搭档可以把它变成真正的代码。
precision intuitive style, that my partner
can actually turn it into real code.
这真是了不起，它将使我的技术沟通达到无法估量的程度。
That is remarkable, it's gonna refine my
technical communication beyond measure.
为什么结对编程如此重要,
Why pair programming is so important as
a team doing these industry reviews with,
你知道的，工程经理和工业界的人来教我们的课程。
you know, engineering managers and
folks in industry for our curriculum.
这个新课程让我们这么做，但是
This new curriculum is
what makes us do it, but
不管他们让我们复习新课程,
whatever they make us
review the new curriculum,
因为和我们合作的是政府机构。
because it's government agency
that we're doing it with.
就是这样，听到他们的声音真让人吃惊
So there you go,
it's astonishing to hear them
谈论他们的高级工程师，他们可能会感到沮丧。
talk about their senior engineers
that they are may be frustrated with.
谁不能用语言表达他们的代码，这是一个巨大的障碍，一个公司。
Who cannot verbalize their code well,
that is a massive hindrance to a company.
所以即使你经验丰富,
So even if you're very seasoned,
这是一个很好的机会，可以有效地表达你的代码。
this is a huge opportunity to
verbalize your code effectively.
所以就这样，就像我说的，你要接受挑战，一个提示，然后
So there we go, as I say, you're
gonna take a challenge, a prompt, and
其中之一就是领航员。
one of this'll mean navigator.
我要口头解释一个策略口头上的伪代码,
I'm gonna be explaining a strategy
verbally, verbal pseudocode,
所以对于一个要用实际代码执行的合伙人来说。
so to speak to a partner who's gonna
be executing it in actual code.
好的，你要这样做，你知道，5分钟的领航员,
Okay, you're going to do it for,
you know, five minutes navigator,
五分钟，司机和女巫结束。
five minutes driver and witch over.
顺便说一句如果你认为你的伴侣走错路了,
If you do think by the way,
your partner's going off on a bad route,
不要阻止他们，不要说我认为那不会起作用。
don't block them,
don't say I think that's not gonna work.
让它发生吧按 Run 你会看到 bug 不是错误,
Let it happen, press Run,
you're gonna see a bug is not a mistake,
你现在知道这个窃听器，可以用来识别问题所在。
the bug is something that you now know can
be used to identify what the problem was.
太棒了,
That's awesome,
你可以成为一个调试器，在那里你已经知道什么是坏的。
you get to be a debugger with them
where you already know what's broken.
还有一些奇怪的错误就像你知道的记号什么的,
And something that weird error that's
like, you know, token whatever,
这不是什么秘密。
now, it's not a mystery.
这是你可以做到的,
It's something you actually can, you know,
幕后的东西是错误的，这实际上是很好的。
what's behind the scene's wrong,
that's pretty nice actually.
好吧顺便说一句有一半的时间是对的
Okay, and by the way,
half the time that may be right and
根据策略，我们走吧，伙计们。
according to the strategy,
there we go people.
我们要结对编程，我们要用旧的风格，我们要去
We're going to pair program and we are
going to do the old style and we're going
通过这个九件事的列表，你们看到了。
to go through this list of nine things,
have reached thing that you see here.
给自己一个积分，总分在1到9之间,
Give yourself a point to get
a total of between one and nine,
是的如果你以前都做过,
yes, so
if you've done all of these before,
这些你都考虑过了，你的总分是，九分。
you've covered all of these,
your score is, total out of, nine.
我不知道这是怎么被切断的，总共9个，如果你做了所有这些,
I don't know how that got cut off, a total
out of nine, if you've done all of these,
你得了9分。
you've got a score of nine.
如果你按顺序做了三个，得分是三，按顺序做了五个,
If you've done three of them in any order,
score of three, five of them in any order,
五分。
score of five.
好的，一旦你知道了你的记录,
Okay, once you know your tally,
各位，我们又回到了老式的哈利波特风格。
people, we are back to the old
school Harry Potter style.